KENNY HONGO

3413 Henderson Rd, Victoria, BC 7789667775 kenny3a38@gmail.com

SUMMARY

Highly motivated computer science student interested in Software Development. Skilled in business communications with 3+ years of experience in Java and Python, seeking an entry-level coop job at a diverse and collaborative workplace. A great listener/team player who understands clients' needs and thinks outside the box to achieve goals. Always open to take advice on learning new skills and technologies.

EDUCATION

Bachelor of Science in Computer Science (BSc)

Expected December 2023

University of Victoria, Victoria, BC, Canada

- Learned the data structures and algorithms in a modern OS and implemented the main components in C
- Applied the human-centered design process and designed a prototype for an online tabletop game interface
- Other Relevant Topics: Database Systems, Artificial Intelligence, Computer Graphics, Digital Logic,
 Quantum Algorithms
- Created my own website in HTML
- Activities and Extracurricular: Japanese Culture Club

Diploma December 2019

Camosun College, Victoria, BC, Canada

- Relevant course work: Introduction to Computer Science (Java)
- Organized an international student orientation and shared personal experience as a panel student

EXPERIENCE

Software Testing Intern

2021 - 2021

Research Center of Computational Mechanics, Tokyo, Japan

- Performed software testing for analyzing the strength of the human body based on cyclist data, collaborating with 2 members of the software developer team.
- Revised the company's software manual and provided reports of shortcomings, corrections, and suggested to 2 development leads to produce better software; software engineers revised code according to my reports.
- Represented software development team of 4 people to explain details of software in a sports technology exhibition; Received engaging attention from participants interested in the inner workings of human body.

Leader/Organizer

2020 - Present

Japanese Culture Club, Victoria, BC, Canada

 Organized culture-related events such as a cultural day, Halloween, BBQ, Karaoke, and conversation cafe with an average of 30 participants; most include prepared activities to do at the beginning.

- Communicated with 6 executive members to conceptualize entertaining plans, aimed for highly engaging events.
- Hosted large-scale events of more than 70, and adapted accordingly to engage and satisfy guests.
- Taught Japanese to a group of 5 people, explaining the culture behind some customs, words, and traditions of Japan.

Content Creator 2021 - Present

Social Media Content Creation, Japan and Canada

- Obtained 400k+ followers on TikTok by creating content about Japanese culture, anime, traditions, and the language.
- Sponsored by 88 Rising and advertised music on TikTok; constructed a video introducing the city of Tokyo.
- Sponsored by LingoDeer and advertised language learning app on TikTok; uploaded a video teaching Japanese words.
- Manage to research topics, plan video content, film, edit, and produce videos.

SKILLS

- Japanese: Native
- English: Proficient
- Interpersonal skills
- Cooperative skills
- Leadership skills
- Time management skills
- Operating Systems: Windows OS| Mac OS| Linux
- Programming Languages: Java|Python|C|C++|C#|SQL|JavaScript|HTML|CSS|SML|R|Matlab
- Software: Visual Studio | Eclipse | Jupyter Notebook
- Microsoft Office Suite: Word | PowerPoint | Excel
- Adobe Suite: Illustrator | Photoshop | Animate
- 2 years of Video editing